If you have done bike or car insurance on Policy Bazaar
but it is
not visible on the Parivahan website or app or
when the traffic police scans your number plate
and the insurance is not shown in it, then
what will you have to do so that your insurance gets
loaded on the Parivahan website or app. I have
also done bike insurance on Policy Bazaar
but it has not yet loaded on the Parivahan site, so first of all
open the Policy Bazaar app and simply
click on the policy,
then whatever insurance you have for your bike or car will be
visible here.  So as soon as you
click on it, it will appear in front of you like this
and simply click on the Need Help option at the bottom of this page.
Now here you have to
tap on Raise a Request.  After that, as soon as you
click on M Transport Issue option,
two options will appear in front of you.  Out of these,
click on the second option Policy is not reflecting at transport site.  You can see that it
is clearly written here that after 7 days
your policy will be updated on the Parivahan website
and until it is updated on the Parivahan site, you must
keep the insurance copy with your car or bike to
show to the traffic police.